(Howard:)Professor Rothman.
This isn't your office anymore.
You're retired.
l think the word you're looking for
is "invisible."
l came to say I'm sorry.
- Don't bother.
- Oh, Amy, please.
(Amy:)I'm so humiliated. I sat there the whole
time we were watching Grease...
(Amy:)- ...thinking you liked the painting.
- l know.
l was a fool from "summer loving"...
...to the last "rama lama lama
ke ding a de dinga a dong."
(Penny:)You're absolutely right.
l should have been honest
and told you the gift was too much.
(Amy:)Yes, too much. Because our friendship
is fundamentally asymmetrical.
l clearly like you
more than you like me.
l don't think you put a number
on how much one person likes another.
l bought you a painting
that's 12 square feet in area.
(Amy:)There's a number.
(Penny:)Amy, come...
(Amy:)If you don't like feet, you can try dollars.
The painting set me back 3 grand.
Three gr?... Oh, my God.